one full day
one full day is how long i've been
working on these boxes as you can see
i've put in the approximate value these
are the new line of barge mystery boxes
and
they're pretty good they are pretty good
so as you can see value 85 diamonds
approximately it depends how you value
things i've done shulker boxes at three
diamonds but scar sells them for two
it's you know so this is a my my what a
decent box
and check it out pretty decent stuff
netherright ingot stuff that's annoying
to craft like observers diamonds there's
an elytra there and then this is the
worst one 38
which is still it's still okay it's just
it's just okay the real prize
is this one
for i'm not going to show exactly what
this box is
but i will open it and show you that
that is all you're going to see
because this
will lead whoever picks it on a little
bit of a quest it's not massive but a
little bit of a quest and then we've got
some other boxes we've got a we got a
holy moly it's average then we got a
whoa
nice box and then we got a bingo bango
you got a box and then we got the big
smashing one
wow we ultra smashing box and check this
out tnt some diamonds
shulker boxes galore two nether right
ingots and then loads of the worst
things to craft in the game pistons and
the like so
we take these over to the barge
and we get these set up but that's not
all i was working on i also have a brand
new
barge backup box which is going to be
sold for five stacks then once we've
done that i've set up
another board
for an updated jungle map we'll come
back to that a little bit later
as i think 15 episodes and enough has
changed in the jungle for us to warrant
another map change so let's load these
up now i am actually going to increase
the price of this because now the
majority of the boxes are over 70
diamonds worth now 55 diamonds per box
meaning there is only one box which
really sucks
and we're also going to add
a couple more of these as the barge
boxes are increasing in number
personally i think the mystery boxes
have been a lot of fun and people seem
to keep coming back which means they are
good value and to be honest there's very
very little risk and now there's a
mystery box with question marks in it
and a bit of a puzzle for them to figure
out and the secret one and all of its
mysteries are also set up and then
finally
the last one
is the backup box
now this is
five stacks of diamonds partly because i
don't actually want to sell it this is
my backup box as much as someone else's
so part of me is hoping this doesn't
sell but at the same time gotta make
those diamonds and if anyone says that
this box is too expensive for five
stacks of diamonds
go and make one yourself
and then tell me if you want to pay the
diamonds okay
go make one yourself and then and then
you'll see
that's not a bad price now last episode
i fell through the barge
and it turns out i've been sleeping on
probably the biggest project on
hermitcraft
and i somehow failed to notice
admittedly my time on the server has
been extremely limited because i've been
so busy
but somehow i managed to miss
this the giant ravager head in the
middle of the shopping district and
somehow a project that's been worked on
for weeks and weeks and weeks by our
very own tango tech i somehow missed it
i mean it's absolutely hilarious that
this enormous project has been literally
right under my nose
check it out this
is decked out a very
enormous complicated
game
that i am going to give a go and it
involves these guys
the handsome ravager so i need to claim
a decked out space
but i haven't got i'm just gonna have to
i'm gonna have to use the chicken head
i haven't got i haven't got any more of
my own head i've used them all in the
barge so
we might need a mem a trip down memory
lane
and we're gonna use the chicken head
there we oh look there we go uh i think
i just do this
take that
and there we have it our first key and
some coins
if you don't know what decked out is
much like i didn't you may want to go
and watch tango's video on how to play
decked out because it's a 10 minute
video and i can't explain it all here
but basically the idea is to collect
items in the dungeon and then there's a
bunch of other stuff so you can see
people have got out of the dungeon with
all of this stuff
i think it's best that we just go in
i've watched the video a couple of times
but i'm still probably gonna do
something wrong so this is the dungeon
key this is the compass and here's some
coins let's go
okay so i've re i've set my respawn at
the bed i i think i have to put this in
here place your shulker box against that
and press the button okay well i didn't
have any cards in there so that's that
here we go
[Laughter]
so i need to look for items i believe so
i have to go through this custom-made
dungeon
looking for artifacts
i don't know where they're
no
oh my goodness
please tell me he can't get me straight
away
oh my goodness he's par fighting to be
already i'm not gonna find anything i
didn't even
i didn't even get a chance okay so the
compass is pointing me
this direction
nothing in here
this is the most insane game i've ever
played do you hear the heartbeat the
heartbeat tells you how likely you are
to get seen by ravagers come on old
school minecraft tricks
there's nothing behind the painting i'm
mildly disappointed i haven't found
anything at all yet this is this is nice
hey hey hey hey is there something in
there
i have to punch out the fire right i'm
not having a lot of luck
finding anything but we should at least
try and follow this compass okay
of course there's a ravager
right where i need to go did he see me
that's definitely where i need to go
if i want to get this compass i don't
know if he can get through there
maybe there's another way round
no
no no no no no no no no
we're close we're too close
oh i might have found it i did
okay i got luke 42.
um so now the goal is to get out with
this loot
ah i can't believe it okay
that ravager fortunately seems to be a
bit stuck
but there's no way i can get through
there without getting hit by it
unless i just go for it
okay okay let's get out of here
we got the loot we got the loot run i
can't run enough
i can't remember the way out
oh this isn't the way out
[Music]
no it's not the way out
the clank
[Music]
yes
when you've completed your dungeon run
press this button
oh
and we got ourselves a loot finder okay
well that was terrifying
so this game is designed
to be played multiple times from what
i've learned so that was just dungeon
run one
and it was terrifying
i now have myself three i've seven coins
a b set
a dragon set
and another set
not bad for a first run
system item so i think i need to
give that back
i think i've done everything right i
think i get to hold on to the coins so i
think i've played the game correctly i
got out with some artifacts it's
probably one of the biggest achievements
in minecraft ever i mean just seeing the
sheer size of it from the outside is so
impressive so we can't actually play
decked out again until we find another
key
as we didn't get enough emeralds to buy
another one i don't know what the
rewards are i barely got out of there
alive but i know that there are keys
hidden around the shopping district
so we just have to
take a good look around now if i was
tango where would i hide them definitely
under this mushroom
i don't know how well hidden they are
no way
we found one i was just i was thinking
if i was tango where would i hide one
definitely in here i don't know how many
of these are around here but we're gonna
save this probably for another episode
if that game didn't make any sense to
you then go and check out tango's video
on how to play decked out
anyway
now that we've had a bit of fun in the
shopping district let's head back
to the base where we need to get some
work done
we'll keep this key in compass for later
on
and now i want to see
what the jungle looks like
now which
last time i did this took me half an
hour
it was um
it wasn't actually that fun so let's
just get on with it and see how we do
didn't actually take as long as i
thought and my oh my have we seen some
changes so take a look at this
it's actually been a while since i
looked at this i wish i'd taken a map a
little bit closer to the start because
this looks like this should be the
second or maybe even the third map
there's two really big areas of change
scars area and ren's area check it out
look at that scars area has filled out
massively mumbo's base is looking clean
compared to what it was and ren's base
has he just changed the entire color of
it
look at that
look at the sheer amount of work
not only to cover it but to gather all
of that blackstone is insane but i also
noticed last time there was a giant e
and i didn't really know what that was
about
but look what's happened since
etho smells alike
no one's filled it in
but i
i can't ignore this
this is this is turned up on the map
someone's written this in
the question is
what does etho
smell like
well
i'm not sure what etho smells like let
me know in the comments what etho smells
like
and we'll add it so it's ready for the
next time
we do another one of these maps it's
good to keep kind of a documentation of
how the jungle's changing because for
example look that that space there is
empty there
there's the uno reverse card right there
but the next time this will be gone so
it's nice to have these little reminders
but i want to continue a little bit of
work on the mansion and what i want to
do is finish this finally just get this
done i want to get this bit done you can
see i've laid it out but i've just been
ignoring it and putting it off for so
long
and i actually realized i don't have the
re i think the reason i actually stopped
this was because i didn't have the
resources for it
so let's quickly go and get the
resources
[Music]
here we go we've got some black concrete
powder we've got some gray concrete
powder and we've got ourselves plenty of
cyan terracotta over here so hopefully
this will be enough
and what we need to do is
just
just get into it just get this done
once this side is done i will feel a lot
happier so and oh my goodness has it
been a long time since we've worked on
the mansion let's get into it because i
want to move
this portal let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
this is looking 10 times better it
actually doesn't look completely
finished and i guess it's not i have a
couple of ideas for what to do down here
now it was meant to be for my portal but
i've since realized since using this
thing it's actually
a pretty terrible place for a portal
there's a clutch portal break
so i actually need to get rid of this
and move it to where i actually use my
base which is in here so i've prepared a
little portal
boom and then hopefully this will link
up this is not where it is
all right it looks like i got a new
portal but actually i think that looks
okay i should have done this from the
start i don't know why i didn't so the
question is what do we do with this
space down here
now the obvious answer to me at the
moment
is i actually need a sugarcane farm
remember back in the start of the season
i had a zero tick sugarcane farm and i
had loads of chests of sugarcane there's
a bit there but as the season's gone on
i thought i'd have enough to last me for
the rest of the season well it's
starting to get a little bit sparse on
the sugarcane front so the plan is to
make something a little bit more
automatic and i think this is a really
natural place for it to go
the other option might be a slime farm
i've never actually made a slime block
sugarcane farm before so this will be
quite interesting for me and i actually
need to do a bit of research i think the
basics of it are though that you set up
a bunch of sugarcane like this and then
you make a slime block machine
that pushes them the difficult part is
getting it all collected
as quickly as possible
so we're looking at a sugar cane farm
about that big
which it doesn't look too massive but
actually that is a decent amount just
there i think there's there's about a
stack here so
one two three it will produce enough
stacks every now and again but i don't
actually know how to make one so between
episodes i'm gonna have to research how
to do this
properly and efficiently especially for
this space need to ask some redstone
people what to do here
so not only will we get a bit of
greenery down here i'm wondering what we
should do up and around here because
while it is neat and tidy now it is
still looking very unfinished so i was
wondering maybe the answer is to do a
bit of like greenery garden up here
always adds a sprinkle of color
i'll keep thinking about it so
now that these two chickens are done
give a present to wiscow and give a
present to mumbo i feel like we can mark
these two as complete so i have added a
little room here completed challenges
so we'd basically just take them and pop
them straight in here so you are the two
first completed chickens because i
killed the other ones by accident it
only feels right that we set up the next
challenge have a breakdown in episode
44. well this is only episode 41
so we're a ways off you yet so you can
stay there let's take one of them out of
this this one out you come
there we go
invent nicknames for all the hermits
well i'm just gonna refer to people for
nicknames all of next episode there are
far too many chickens in these little
cubby holes they all need rescuing i
want to start getting the chickens
together because they are literally just
all hidden in here and i'm going to miss
them if i'm not careful
now we've kind of come back to basics
base basics oh
the mighty pun i basically took a break
from the mansion just because it looks
very complete but it's not and it was it
was a difficult thing to work on but
since we've come back and we've started
doing a little work it's kind of spurred
me on to want to finish
and that's led
to my biggest mistake
thinking
thinking is a mistake because i started
can it be bigger the answer is
yes
it can definitely be bigger and then the
question became
how much bigger
we do have a lot of space round the back
and i've been really wondering if it's
worth even trying this
but
if i take a stack of blocks and we check
how much further higher we can go
i believe it's a substantial amount of
blocks that we have left
yep we can go a lot higher so now the
question becomes not
can it be bigger but
do we want to go bigger because it could
it could go even taller look at that
that's not a small amount and i can
almost picture it now in my head
another section of the mansion above
this one i'm torn between
wanting the most epic and biggest and
amazing and most detailed thing that
i've ever built and knowing it's a
massive mistake to touch it it's it's
looking amazing but at the same time it
can be bigger
but does bigger make better
i don't know i'd love to hear some
opinions on this i may even start
messing with this in a creative world to
see if it's even worth exploring this
but the last thing we want to do
is start something that we're not gonna
finish
so i'm gonna have a think about this one
there's a lot of potential a lot of very
scary potential it doesn't have to go
all the way up to build height this
mansion is wider than i expected so
there is room to make it taller than
expected as well but one thing's for
sure we can't start something new
until we've finished what we've just
started this is the sort of stuff you're
supposed to get done in your first few
episodes
but somehow i've ended up here doing it
anyway and also i've added a new thing
to the barge i feel like i'm doing this
every episode now but the barge is my
little project and what i've got here
are firework boxes and i'm going to sell
them at an extreme discount what on
earth
hello i am mumbo jumbo ni that's mumbo's
real face okay it works better further
away that is
extremely detailed
seeing as i've seen mumbo fairly
recently
i mean that's really weird obviously
that's not his real mustache he looks so
concerned mumbo are you okay
well you're clearly not okay you're a
red cactus
sometimes things on the server throw you
a curveball and i've got to admit that
picture of mumbo
that's the definition of a curveball
right right here oh i filled this with
junk we're gonna put in our firework
boxes
rocket box
how much would that be worth
the shulker box is worth two diamonds
so we'll make it we'll make six diamonds
for a full box i think that's a pretty
good price it's the convenience that's
the main thing and you get to keep a
shulker box as well
so i think that is all we have time for
today i do have a slight update on the
ravager game decked out that tango has
been making
i have found myself a couple of boxes
well actually not just a couple i found
three boxes so
next episode or between episodes i am
going to do a
couple of decked out runs and see what
we can get i wonder if people will like
this game this will be the first time
this episode will be the first time that
you see it
and we're very close to being able to
get another box so i'll probably end the
episode here waiting for the new decked
out box
so that we can play decked out next
episode as well unless it's closed for
maintenance which it probably
looks like it's close for maintenance
okay
we'll see you next episode anyway bye